Click at the Overview tab at the top of
your course dashboard.
cue-2
Here you can have an aerial view of your
course pages, individual students,
cue-3
assessment scores, and recommended
actions.
cue-4
If you navigate to the Students tab, it
will give you a full roster of your
cue-5
enrolled students.
cue-6
You can use the search feature and
progress and proficiency level to locate
cue-7
certain students
cue-8
or filter by student types on the
right-hand side.
cue-9
For example, I want to see for those who
have mostly completed the activities what
cue-10
their common mistakes are.
cue-11
Then, I can select progress greater or
equal than 90% and proficiency medium and
cue-12
low.
cue-13
To view individual student insight, click
on the student. You will have a more
cue-14
detailed information breakdown.
cue-15
Go to their Progress tab. You can then
select or search for a specific page or
cue-16
activity.
cue-17
After you click on the page, you will see
the student's attempt history.
cue-18
This includes number of attempts, when
they started each attempt, and when they
cue-19
submitted it for scored activities. Click
into one attempt to see the student's
cue-20
answers and how each response was
evaluated. This view can help you identify
cue-21
where a student may have misunderstood a
concept or whether they need support or
cue-22
additional attempts.